# **NURIDDNOV KHURSHIDBEK**

FRONTEND DEVELOPER



+998 97 108 20 04

khurshidbeknuriddnov@gmail.com

Uzbekistan, Tashkent city

khurshidbek-web.uz

## **PROFILE**

I am Nuriddinov Khurshidbek, 20 years old, and I have been studying web programming for a year and a half. Currently, I participated in several real projects, I worked at md.uz company, I left there because of my university. I need a remote job.

# SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS(Tailwind, Bootstrap, SCSS)
- JavaScript
- Webpack
- .
- Redux (Redux toolkit)
- TanstackQuery (Axios)
- GIT-GITHUB

# EDUCATION

### SECONDARY SCHOOL

Najot ta'lim 2022 - 2023

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY
TUIT(Tashkent unversty information technolog

# EXPERIENCE

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Really Great Company

2023 - Present

I recently participated in the project of md.uz company

dachivgorax.uz. My task was as follows.

- Page Javouts
- Using Axios for API interaction
- Implementing CRUD operations on admin pages
- Working with leaflet maps, polygons, geojson, geoman
- Close team communcation with backend developers
- Used technologies: React, React Router, ReduxToolkit, Tailwind,
  MUI, Axios,TanstackQuery, Rest APIt

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Really Great Company

2023 - october

Frontend Developer at Freelance, Tashkent

November 2021 — January 2023

I freelanced as a Frontend Developer, focusing on HTML, CSS, and  $\,$ 

JavaScript. I was

responsible for crafting visually appealing, responsive landing pages

Nuriddnov Khurshidbek Page 1 of 1